In the current version, the default physics attribute is the name of the English version, and the name is the name of the kind of fabric, and the physics attribute is measured.
In the Fabric folder in the window of the drawing, it is also named in English.
The mouse is stopped on the shrink chart, and you can see the preview of the fabric placed on the ball.
Click the Add button, select the downloaded and compressed Fabric folder, and you can import the default fabric file with a Chinese name.
At this time, the mouse is stopped on the shrink chart of the fabric, and you can see that the name has been changed to a Chinese name.
Next, replace the default file in the system with the translated file.
Click the default file in the settings menu in the main menu, and set the default plant folder to the translated Fabric folder path.
After the replacement, you need to restart Marvelous Designer.
Now open the preview of the physics attribute.
You can see that the name has been changed to Chinese.
Open the Fabric folder in the
You can see the Chinese name and purpose of each type of fabric.
You can choose to use according to your needs.
You can also use the default Asset Manager.
In this case, you can choose the default Asset Manager.
Go to the Asset Manager and select the default Asset Manager.
Click the Temporary Login icon.
You can name the type of parse.
Click the Asset Manager icon and set the default mask to 0.
In the final page, you can see that the value of the number of lines you want to color in the source of the code is 0.
Click Founder.
You can see that you have a different sense of taste in the file.
The results are the same for all sources of value of the child.